Guide to the St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio records, 1950-1998 MS2004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Non-print media, 1950-1988; MS2004 Series 4
  - Photographs: Lunch Theatre, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 ca. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: A Christmas Carol, Jogues, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: A Christmas Carol and Peter and the Wolf, Nan Paolillo, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Peter and the Wolf, Nan Paolillo, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Peter and the Wolf, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: A Christmas Carol, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Eugene Onegin, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Nan Randall, St. Mark's Dance Co., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Passacaille, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Peter and the Wolf, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Sarah, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Sarah, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Sarah, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Dance Studio Brochure, 1978 June (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Dance Studio Brochure, 1978 June (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: A Christmas Carol, Jogues, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Recital, Geneva Portluck, St. Mark's Dance Studio, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: A Christmas Carol, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Hobbit Fantasy, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1980 ca. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Dance Company, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Workshop, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1985 June (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Mary Craighill, 1987 ca. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Vet and Airman's Hospital, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Lunch Theatre, Julie Craighill, St, Mark's Dance Company, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Lunch Theatre, St. Mark's Dance Company, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Mary Craighill, n.d., undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Junior Company and Dance Studio, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Slides: Gospel Song, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Slides: Rehearsal, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 ca. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Slides: Surrexit Christus, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 ca. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Slides: Bizet, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Slides: Workshops, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1970 ca. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Slides: St. Mark's Junior Company, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Slides: A Christmas Carol, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Slides: Lunch Theatre, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Slides: Peter and the Wolf, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Slides: Craighill Studio, n.d., undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Negatives: Mary Craighill, 1950-1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Negatives: Rejoice, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Negatives: Stages of Man, St. Mark's Dance Company, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Negatives: Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972 ca. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Negatives: Bear Tracks, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Negatives: Where the Wild Things Are, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Negatives: Wolf Trap, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1975 ca. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Negatives: A Christmas Carol, Nan Paolillo, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Negatives: Peter and the Wolf, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Negatives: St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Negatives: Nan Randall, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Negatives: Peter and the Wolf, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Negatives: Sarah, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Negatives: A Christmas Carol, Jogues, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Negatives: St. Mark's Dance Studio Brochure, June, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Negatives: A Christmas Carol, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Negatives: Lunch Theatre, Julie Craighill, St. Mark's Dance Company, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Negatives: Lunch Theatre, St. Mark's Dance Company, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Negatives: St. Mark's Dance Studio, n.d., undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Audiotapes: Ted Shawn, A Century of American Dance, Washington Ballet Guild Lecture Series, March, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Audiotapes: Nancy Surrick, The Flower and On the Verge, 1981 ca. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Audiotapes: Joseph Ott, Sun-Copy, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Audiotapes: Reflections of a Dancing Girl, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Audiotapes: Footnotes, William Brooks, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Audiotapes: William Weber, Jazz Mass Rehearsal Music, (Gloria), undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Audiotapes: Unidentified, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: Ted Shawn, A Century of American Dance, Washington Ballet Guild Lecture Series, 1962 March (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: Ted Shawn, A Century of American Dance, Washington Ballet Guild Lecture Series, 1962 March (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: Ted Shawn, A Century of American Dance, Washington Ballet Guild Lecture Series, 1962 March (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: Ted Shawn, A Century of American Dance, Washington Ballet Guild Lecture Series, 1962 March (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: Controversy, 1967 April (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: St. Mark's Dance Company Copyright Newsreal, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: Dance Films Association Conference, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: Dance Films Association Conference, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Oversized records, 1950-1990; MS2004 Series 5
  This series contains administrative Records, performances, programs, and special events, and non-print media. The materials consist of fliers, brochures and posters. The series dates from ca. 1950 to 1990.
  - Administrative Records: Washington Post Article, 1961 April (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Records: Sunday Star Article, 1966 May (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Records: Northern Virginia Sun Article, 1971 December (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Records: Hill Rag Article, 1981 October (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: A Christmas Service, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company Concert Performance, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Arlington Dance Theatre Christmas Concert, 1973 ca. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Arlington Dance Theatre in Concert, 1974 ca. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: St. Mark's Dance Company Showcase Performance, 1977 ca. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Summerdance, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Dance Fest '83, 1983 May (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Arlington Dance Theatre Junior Company, n.d., undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Lunch Theatre, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: A Christmas Carol and Peter and the Wolf, n.d., undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Unidentified, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events Files: Unidentified, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Non-Print Media: Mary Craighill, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Non-Print Media: Mary Craighill, Workshop, 1971 ca. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Non-Print Media: Arlington Dance Theatre, 1973 ca. --1974 ca. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Non-Print Media: Arlington Dance Theatre, 1973 ca. --1974 ca. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Non-Print Media: A Christmas Carol and Peter and the Wolf, Nan Paolillo, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Non-Print Media: St. Mark's Dance Studio Brochure, June, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Non-Print Media: A Christmas Carol, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: Washington Contemporary Dance Foundation, Inc.'s Joint Dance Concert at Roosevelt Auditorium, May, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: Mary Craighill and Company, 1961 May (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: The Naval Academy Christian Association Presents the St. Mark's Dance Company, 1971 Novermber (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: Lunch Theatre, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: Gala Concert-Dinner-Disco, 1981 May (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: Prince George's Publick Playhouse, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Performances, Programs, and Special Events: Washington Celebrates National Dance Week, April, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Non-Print Media: Mary Craighill with Robert Fabik, 1950 ca. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Non-Print Media: St. Mark's Dance Company, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Administrative records: St. Mark's Church Dance Studio and Dance Company, 1981 ca. (Oversize 30, Folder 1)
  - Performances, programs, and special events: Lunch Theatre, 1980 (Oversize 30, Folder 2)
  - Performances, programs, and special events: Christmas Revels, 1983 (Oversize 30, Folder 3)
  - Performances, programs, and special events: Unidentified, 1990 ca. (Oversize 30, Folder 4)
  - Non-print media: Mary Craighill with Robert Fabrik, 1965 ca. (Oversize 30, Folder 5)
  - Non-print media: Alleluia, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1963 (Oversize 30, Folder 6)